{
    "subject": "resource/Drew_Sidora",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthDate",
    "object": "1985-05-01",
    "human_readable": "Drew Sidora was born on May 1, 1985.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8986809849739075,
            "question": "When was Drew Sidora born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7830111384391785,
            "question": "Is Drew Sidora a May baby?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7612892985343933,
            "question": "What is Drew Sidora's birth date?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7231220006942749,
            "question": "In what month was Drew Sidora born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6840433478355408,
            "question": "Did Drew Sidora have a birthday recently?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6250420212745667,
            "question": "How old is Drew Sidora?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6229546666145325,
            "question": "What day of the month was Drew Sidora born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3989519476890564,
            "question": "What year did Drew Sidora enter the world?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.20822514593601227,
            "question": "If today is October 26th, how many days older than Drew Sidora are you?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.04441627115011215,
            "question": "What month comes after May?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Drew Sidora was born on May 1, 1985.",
            "html": "dbpedia_5591_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If today is October 26th, how many days older than Drew Sidora are you?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5591_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What year did Drew Sidora enter the world?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5591_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What day of the month was Drew Sidora born?",
            "html": "dbpedia_5591_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5591_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5591_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5591_23.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5591_24.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5591_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5591_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5591_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5591_57.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5591_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_5591_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the response in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThis is because all four documents contain information that confirms Drew Sidora's birthdate as May 1, 1985."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe information across the documents consistently states that Drew Sidora was born on May 1, 1985."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n    \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}